export const clubs = [
  {
    id: 1,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which club has the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
    options: ["Barcelona", "Liverpool", "Real Madrid", "AC Milan"],
    answer: "Real Madrid",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which club is nicknamed 'The Red Devils'?",
    options: ["Arsenal", "Liverpool", "Manchester United", "Chelsea"],
    answer: "Manchester United",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which Italian club is known as 'The Old Lady'?",
    options: ["Inter", "AC Milan", "Roma", "Juventus"],
    answer: "Juventus",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    category: "Clubs",
    question:
      "Which club did Lionel Messi join after leaving Barcelona in 2021?",
    options: ["Man City", "PSG", "Inter", "Chelsea"],
    answer: "PSG",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which Premier League club plays at Anfield?",
    options: ["Everton", "Liverpool", "Chelsea", "Arsenal"],
    answer: "Liverpool",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which German club has won the most Bundesliga titles?",
    options: ["Dortmund", "Schalke", "Leipzig", "Bayern Munich"],
    answer: "Bayern Munich",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which club did Cristiano Ronaldo join in 2009?",
    options: ["Juventus", "Real Madrid", "Man United", "Sporting"],
    answer: "Real Madrid",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which Spanish club is known as 'Los Colchoneros'?",
    options: ["Barcelona", "Sevilla", "Real Madrid", "Atlético Madrid"],
    answer: "Atlético Madrid",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which French club has the most Ligue 1 titles?",
    options: ["PSG", "Monaco", "Marseille", "Saint-Étienne"],
    answer: "Saint-Étienne",
  },
  {
    id: 0,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which English club has won the most Premier League titles?",
    options: ["Chelsea", "Liverpool", "Arsenal", "Manchester United"],
    answer: "Manchester United",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which club won the 2021 Champions League?",
    options: ["Real Madrid", "Chelsea", "Bayern Munich", "Liverpool"],
    answer: "Chelsea",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which South American club produced Neymar?",
    options: ["Flamengo", "Boca Juniors", "Santos", "River Plate"],
    answer: "Santos",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which club has the most FA Cup titles?",
    options: ["Man United", "Chelsea", "Liverpool", "Arsenal"],
    answer: "Arsenal",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which Portuguese club is known as 'The Eagles'?",
    options: ["Porto", "Braga", "Benfica", "Sporting CP"],
    answer: "Benfica",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which Dutch club is based in Amsterdam?",
    options: ["PSV", "Feyenoord", "Twente", "Ajax"],
    answer: "Ajax",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which MLS club did David Beckham play for?",
    options: ["Seattle", "LA Galaxy", "Chicago Fire", "NYCFC"],
    answer: "LA Galaxy",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which club plays at the Allianz Stadium?",
    options: ["Juventus", "Bayern", "Inter", "Dortmund"],
    answer: "Juventus",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which Belgian club developed Kevin De Bruyne?",
    options: ["Genk", "Anderlecht", "Brugge", "Liège"],
    answer: "Genk",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    category: "Clubs",
    question: "Which team won the first-ever Premier League in 1992?",
    options: ["Liverpool", "Arsenal", "Chelsea", "Manchester United"],
    answer: "Manchester United",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    category: "Clubs",
    question:
      "Which club is nicknamed 'The Invincibles' for their 2003–04 season?",
    options: ["Arsenal", "Chelsea", "Liverpool", "United"],
    answer: "Arsenal",
  },
];
